I'm now going to pursue working on Pam's bikini line.
In many times, incidences in my salon I have women that want all the hair off.
And when the hair is dark, like I said before, I'm going to tell them I think, and this is my opinion, I think laser is going to be the better choice for you.
But when it's a woman that has sporadic hair on the side or here and there, strays and some cleanup work, I would advise electrology.
And especially if that hair is light in color because energy of a laser is not going to work on lighter hair.
It doesn't have the melanin for the laser to be attracted to it and cause the heat to go into the follicle and destroy the germitive cells.
But when it comes to electrology, each hair no matter what the color is, it's going to work on.
So in that fashion we're going to go in and we're going to look, assess the area.
Pam's hair is not very dark.
It really is kind of a dark blonde.
But the nice thing about Pam is that she has light skin.
So this would work on a laser.
But not at the best potential like a white skinned person and a dark, dark haired person.
So she wants electrology.
She really believes in it.
She's had great success with it and that's what we're going to do.
So now we're just going to slide each one of these down, this probe, down each one of these follicles.
And this hair is a little heavier.
And this is they call terminal sexual hair.
It's deeper and it's a little stronger.
As you can see if I was to hold up that hair, that it's deeper than a lot of the other hairs in the body.
If you measure on the probe how deep it is, so that tells you just how deep your insertion should be.